<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Thoughtful Goose</title>
    <link>https://goose.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Thoughtful Goose</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://goose.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Masculine and Feminine Aspects and Roles</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/thoughts/masculine-and-feminine-aspects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 10:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/thoughts/masculine-and-feminine-aspects/</guid>
      <description>I had been hoping to publish a direct follow-up to my first article, The Purpose of Life, but that&amp;rsquo;s taking more time to flesh out than expected. I&amp;rsquo;ve been considering applying to graduate school while taking a class and also procrastinating on Twitter. One of those procrastinations inspired this post here, which will eventually fit in with the overall theme (hopefully).
Controversial Conservative Ideas on Twitter In this last week there has been a lot written regarding a collection of public thinkers that share a loose connection by way of having shared the experience of upsetting the sensibilities of vehement progressives and leftists; they&amp;rsquo;ve been publicly dubbed the Intellectual Dark Web and I don&amp;rsquo;t think the branding has been helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/about/</guid>
      <description>The Author I am Shawn Marincas, Gooseus is my online alias and pen name (pronounced &amp;ldquo;goosey-yus&amp;rdquo;). It&amp;rsquo;s a Latinized version of my HS nickname (which was not a reference to Top Gun) which I adapted for my Xbox Live handle in college after watching Gladiator. Now I just like how it makes me sound like a real philospher. Yes, I am a nerd.
I&amp;rsquo;m originally from Brick, New Jersey and am now a resident of Portland, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purpose of Life</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/thoughts/the-purpose-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 05:03:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/thoughts/the-purpose-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what I mean by &amp;ldquo;The Purpose of Life&amp;rdquo;. What I&amp;rsquo;m to referring here is the chemical process we call Life; a unique process that any intelligent beings would observe while studying our planet. This is Life with a capital &amp;lsquo;L&amp;rsquo;, and while it includes you and every other living being on the planet, this isn&amp;rsquo;t about making value judgments regarding what you are doing with your personal life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>