<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Thoughtful Goose</title>
    <link>https://goose.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Thoughtful Goose</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 10:34:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://goose.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Masculine and Feminine</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/thoughts/masculine-and-feminine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 10:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/thoughts/masculine-and-feminine/</guid>
      <description>I had been hoping to publish a direct follow-up to my first article, The Purpose of Life, but that&amp;rsquo;s taking more time to flesh out than expected, partly because I&amp;rsquo;ve been procrastinating on Twitter. One of those procrastinations inspired this post here, which will hopefully fit in with the overall theme at some point.
Much of this was written after two conversations, one that took place between myself and @catvalente, someone I do not know from Twitter, and then one with my girlfriend, Liesa, about the first conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/about/</guid>
      <description>The Author I am Shawn Marincas, Gooseus is my online alias and pen name (pronounced &amp;ldquo;goosey-yus&amp;rdquo;). It&amp;rsquo;s a Latinized version of my HS nickname (which was not a reference to Top Gun) which I adapted for my Xbox Live handle in college after watching Gladiator. Now I just like how it makes me sound like a real philospher. Yes, I am a nerd.
I&amp;rsquo;m originally from Brick, New Jersey and am now a resident of Portland, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purpose of Life</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/thoughts/the-purpose-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 05:03:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/thoughts/the-purpose-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what I mean by &amp;ldquo;The Purpose of Life&amp;rdquo;. What I&amp;rsquo;m to referring here is the chemical process we call Life; a unique process that any intelligent beings would observe while studying our planet. This is Life with a capital &amp;lsquo;L&amp;rsquo;, and while it includes you and every other living being on the planet, this isn&amp;rsquo;t about making value judgments regarding what you are doing with your personal life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>