<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Thoughtful Goose</title>
    <link>https://goose.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Thoughtful Goose</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:08:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://goose.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/about/</guid>
      <description>The Author I am Shawn Marincas, Gooseus is my online alias and pen name (pronounced &amp;ldquo;goosey-yus&amp;rdquo;). It&amp;rsquo;s a Latinized version of my HS nickname (which was not a reference to Top Gun) which I adapted for my Xbox Live handle in college after watching Gladiator. Now I just like how it makes me sound like a real philospher. Yes, I am a nerd.
I&amp;rsquo;m originally from Brick, New Jersey and am now a resident of Portland, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas</title>
      <link>https://goose.us/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/ideas/</guid>
      <description> The Downward Spiral of Discourse - Negative feedback loops in social trust and opinion of each other
 How cognitive false assumptions have created negative feedback loops by way of social media  Sol-Earth Foundation (Earth Resilience Foundation)
 Patron Foundation  Generate funding for Foundation projects Generate interest in Foundation projects Find Foundation group members  Knowledge Foundation  The University (Concent)  Gather and disseminate knowledge Self-sufficient by using (and testing) the gathered knowledge Robust information architecture and backup internet Home for Foundation and all projects  The Moonolith (Moonument)  Knowledge capsule and radio server meant to be placed on the moon Highly dense information structures Highly accessible by any intelligence with scientific civilization requirements  Symbolic language Information theory Radio technology      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://goose.us/thoughts/something-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goose.us/thoughts/something-something/</guid>
      <description>So what to write&amp;hellip; I need a plan of action.
There is an application I want to fill out:
1) Look at PhD Website for Systems Science.
2) Ask another person for a reference.
3) Ask a third person for a reference.
4) Write the reference skeleton for Mike to modify.
5) Write personal reference and essay for acceptance.
6) Send GRE scores to school.
7) Make sure transcripts are at school.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>